Seven steps to a perfect accent. One, yep, I have an accent, I want to change it, and
I'm sure this program will work for me. Two, I'm making a conscious effort to
apply the techniques in an orderly, step-by-step manner. Three, I have taken an
inventory of the sounds and rhythm patterns. Four, I am keeping a daily log
of the what factor. Five, I record myself once a week, compare it with my original
recording, and take specific and detailed notes of changes. 6. When I talk to
people, I consciously and conscientiously apply the techniques. 7. I read aloud for
15 minutes a day with a phonetic transcription or imitate an audio text.
The Pledge. It's not the duration, it's the consistency. I'm training my mouth,
lips, tongue, and mind.